≪（千鶴）♪♪～気持ちのいい朝
３丁目　目印は　にゃんこよ～→
All right! Today I'll make my deliveries without getting lost!
よーし　今日こそ迷子にならず
配達をする　…って　あれ？
Oh?
Good morning.
（潤平）おはようございます
おはよう
Morning.
いや　あの～　何で
声かけてくれないんですか？
Um, why won't you talk to me?
I didn't want to stop you if you were skipping town.
いや　朝から夜逃げだったら
邪魔しちゃ悪いし…
I'm not!
違います　違います
Then why all the bags?
じゃ　どうしたの？　その大荷物
Well, we're leaving on a school trip today.
実はその　今日から修学旅行でして
へえ～　いいなあ
That's nice!
≪（マサ）ニャ～
今　ニャ～言った？
Did I just hear a meow?
いや　ヘクションですってば
No, it was a sneeze!
すいません　集合時間に
遅れちまうんで　ほんじゃ
Sorry, I mustn't be late!
Bye!
Bye...
Have a good trip.
行ってらっしゃい
Bring me a souvenir!
おみやげ　よろしくね
ano sora e kimi to hashiri dasou
I'll dash towards the sky.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete ageru...
I'll make all your wishes come true.
areya koreya to oshiyosete
Troubles engulfed me at every turn,
itsuno manika nichijou goodbye
and my normal days were gone before I knew it.
anote konote neko tedasuke
I help the cats with this and that.
guruguru mawaru triangle
The triangle whirls around me.
ukauka shite rarenai
There's no time to waste.
isoganakya ikenaitte
I'd better hurry.
kimi eno omoi mo sou nandaka karamawari de
My feelings towards you are spinning in circles.
tsuite nai koto mo
An unfortunate event
ookina chance ni naru kamo shirenai!
might prove to be a big opportunity!
kimi no egao ga mireta nara kitto
If I get to see your smile,
nyan toka narutte mae wo mukeru yo
I'll try to believe everything will be fine.
masa ni nyanderful
It's really a wonderful cat power.
itsuka kono te todokimasu you ni
May this hand reach you some day.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete miseru yo
I'll really make all your wishes come true.
Cat 07!
Wait  For  Me  Before It  Gets  Dark
≪（晴彦）ウッハ～ッ　ついに来たさ
あこがれの地→
We're finally here!
The place I've longed for, filled with exciting events! Kyoto!
イベント満載の都　京都ーッ！
I should check out the maiko and the miko...
Note: The dancing girls and the priestesses.
舞子はんと　巫女はんと
Nah, I'll start with the bus tour guide!
いやいや　まずはバスガイドはんを
基本ルートにおさえとかなあきまへん
（晃太）へえ…
Hey, we're here.
ほら　着いたぞ
Our deal is finished now.
これで約束は果たしたかんな
（マサ）おおきに
Thanks.
You've been a great help.
ほんま助かったわ
けど　ホントにここで大丈夫かよ
But will you really be all right from here on?
心配ご無用　このご恩は
決して忘れませんさかい　ほな
Don't worry.
I'll never forget the favor you've done for me.
Bye.
ニャ～オ
ふう　出がけに
押しかけられたときにゃあ
Receiving that request at the last minute made me nervous, but...
どうしようかと思ったが…
Master, I heard that you'll be traveling to Kyoto?
《（タマ）ダンナ
京都にご旅行ですって？》
Then please take Masa-nii with you.
《ぜひ　このマサにいを》
《一緒に里帰りさせとくれやす》
Let me visit my home with you.
まッ　これで久々の自由の身
Well, now I have my long-forgotten freedom again!
I'll use this time to get close to Mizuno!
このチャンスにぜひ
水野とお近づきに…
Hey, there he is.
What are you doing, Kousaka-kun?
（楓）高坂君　どうしたの？
バス乗り遅れるよ
You'll miss the bus.
えッ　おッ　おう
Y-Yeah.
（バスガイド）え～　常盤高校
２年３組の皆さん　おいでやす
Members of Class 2-3 from Tokiwa High School!
Welcome!
Enjoy your four-day trip here in Kyoto.
３泊４日の京都の旅　ごゆるりと
Rock on!
盛り上がるどすえーッ！
はい　よくできました→
Very good!
Moving on, this is the best place to break your leg, the Kiyomizu-dera.
Note: Tradition held that if a person jumped from Kiyomizu-dera and survived, his wished would be granted.
でもって　サクサクと…
こちらが飛び降りる舞台ナンバーワン→
清水寺でございます
わあ～　やっぱ高いね
水野　おい　危ねえって
It's really high!
Mizuno! Be careful!
What if you fell?!
落ちたらどうなると思ってんだ
Then jump off and show us, Junpei.
じゃ　試しに飛び降りてみ　潤平
何すんだ　お前！
Wh-What was that for?!
You wuss.
このヘタレが
Do you happen to be...
もしかして…
scared of heights?
怖いのか？
Wh-Wh-Wh-What?!
何だとーッ？
高坂君　器用
That was a neat trick, Kousaka-kun.
ヘタレっつうのは
ヘタこいたヤツの…
A wuss is more like...
Hey, there's a kitty!
あッ　猫ちゃんがいる
（子猫）ニャ～オ
Kousaka Junpei!
高坂潤平はーん
Is Mr. Kousaka around?
高坂はん　おらへんか？
I wonder why he's meowing so much?
何　鳴いてるのかな？
〈なぜ　俺の名を？〉
How does he know my name?
あれ　高坂君？
Oh? Kousaka-kun?
おおきに　もう３日も
食べてなかったからな　お父はん
Thank you.
We haven't eaten for three days, right, Dad?
（親猫）恩にきますえ
We really appreciate this.
So, where did you hear about me?
なあ　俺のこと　どこで？
マサにいが街で言うとった
Masa-nii was talking about you in town.
I heard that you help cats even though you're allergic to them.
聞きましたで　ご自分が
猫アレルギーいうんも顧みず
〈まさかアイツ　俺のこと
京都中にふれまわって…〉
Don't tell me he's spreading my name all over Kyoto.
There he is.
（猫達）おったで　こっちや
マジか　おい！
For real?!
This is Kyoto Imperial Palace.
こちらは京都御所でございます→
From the mid-Kamakura era through the early-Meiji era, this palace is where Emperors—
京都御所は鎌倉時代中期から
明治時代初期まで…
You gotta be kidding me!
…ったく　冗談じゃねえ
うん？
天満宮～
Tenman-gu!
Note: A shrine devoted to the deified scholar Sugawara no Michizane.
ほお～　学業の神様ね
The god of academics, huh?
おめえバカだし　お守り買って
You're an idiot, so buy some good-luck charms here!
…って潤平　いないし
He's gone.
Here.
はい
おおきに
Thank you!
Thanks to you, my owner will finally get into college this year!
これで　ウチのご主人様も
今年こそ浪人脱出にゃーん
はい　おめでとさん
Congratulations.
Kinkaku-ji!
Note: The Temple of the Golden Pavilion.
金閣寺
はい　チーズ
Say "Cheese."
Спасибо.
Note: Russian for "Thank you."
スパシーボ
Спасибо.
Loading...
Ryoan-ji!
Note: The Temple of the Peaceful Dragon.
龍安寺
Japanese men are amazing!
I-I can't stand this anymore!
我慢の限界だーッ！
Nijo Castle!
二条城
Oh? Where's Kousaka-kun?
あれ？　高坂君は…
（晴彦）なんか気分わりいって
He said he wasn't feeling well.
He's resting in the bus.
（晃太）バスで休んでるってよ
ええ～　大丈夫かな
Is he all right?
This afro's really big.
アフロちゃん
すごい　ボヨヨ～ン
I have no other choice.
しゃあねえ　背に腹は代えられん
ええと…
Let's see...
「こちらＪ　至急連絡取りたし
俺のケーバンは…」
"Please call immediately.
My number is..."
[TEL]（琴音）いやん
そんなの知ってますよ
Come on, I know it already.
…って　あのさ　頼みあんだけど
So... hey, I have a favor to ask.
Yes?
[TEL]はい？
（住職）おや？　若い子に
はやっとる遊びなのかのう
Oh?
Is this the new trend among kids nowadays?
Gotta check it out!
チェーック！
（朱莉）もう　まだなの？
Come on! Are you done yet?!
重い　生あったかい！
（琴音）シーッ
He's so heavy! He's warm!
（タマ）ニャン　ニャン　ニャン
But still!
[TEL]いや　だから！
ニャン？
It's a big problem for me!
こっちは迷惑してんだよ
アイツ捕まえて
噂ばらまくの　やめさせねえと
I need to catch him and stop him from spreading my name!
But I don't know much about where Masa-nii lives.
[TEL]（タマ）けど　僕も
よく知らねえんですよ
[TEL]マサにいの素性
ああ？
[TEL]（タマ）なんでも
京都でトラブルに巻き込まれて
I think he got in trouble in Kyoto and came to stay with friends in Tokyo.
[TEL]しばらく　こっちの知り合いに
身を寄せてたとか…
Oh yeah...
[TEL]あッ　そうそう
何だ？
What is it?
As souvenirs, Saikyo-style pickled sablefish, or Nishijin's—
おみやげには　ぜひ本場の
銀ダラ西京漬け　もしくは西陣の…
He's so useless!
使えねえ
All together...
（生徒達）せーの　いただきまーす！
Let's eat!
おお　仲居さん　おばんでーす
Hey, Nakai-san!
Good evening!
マメだな　お前
You're so diligent.
I don't want to hear that from someone who has a girlfriend.
≪（晴彦）彼女いるヤツに
言われたかねえよ
高坂君　大丈夫？
えッ？
Are you all right, Kousaka-kun?
I can get the teacher if you're not feeling well.
調子悪かったら
先生に言ってあげようか？
あッ　いや　平気
No, I'm fine.
〈水野　優しい〉
She's really kind.
Oh yeah, Ichinose-senpai's home is around here.
そうそう　一ノ瀬先輩の実家って
こっちなんだよ
えッ　実家？
先輩　ホントは京都の人なの
Her home?
She's originally from Kyoto.
ご両親はこっちにいるんだって
へえ　そうなんだ
Her parents still live here.
Really.
Damn Junpei, you're such a slob!
〈潤平のヤロー
デレデレしやがって〉
How can I deal with my anger...
〈どうしてくれよう
この煮えたぎる怒りを…〉
Kana-chan! Your hair!
カナちゃん　髪の毛！
Damn!
Male
Public Bath
Female
はあ～ッ　いいなあ
I love this school trip.
修学旅行　サイコー！
It's the best!
（晴彦達）穴探せ　穴！
必ずあるはずだ→
Keep looking!
There must be one somewhere!
I know the women's bath is on the other side!
女子風呂なのは分かってんだ
気分　壊れた
Damn idiots.
They're such children.
（晃太）…たく　ガキだよな
女は大事にしなきゃダメだろ
You should treat women better.
見せ物扱いなんて
もってのほかだぜ
They're not sex objects.
晃太　お前…
Kouta, you—
Found one!
≪（晴彦）あったぞーッ
This is it!
ここだ　ここからでバッチリだ
Perfect!
It's show time.
じゃ　そういうワケで…
So, anyway...
うおーッ！
どういうワケだよ！
What the hell!?
Let me through!
俺は大事に拝ませてもらう
仏像か！
Curse you!
平気平気　大して焦げてないよ
It's all right.
Not much got burned.
このくらいなら　おかしくないって
It doesn't look odd.
うん…
どうかした？
Is something wrong?
あのさあ　楓　あんた…
H-Hey Kaede, what do you—
あの…　あの…
やっぱりダメだ～
I can't say it.
さっきから変だよ　カナちゃん
You've been acting strange lately, Kana-chan.
Yeah! A clear view!
（晃太）惜しい　湯気でよく見えん
（晴彦）もう代わってけれよ　晃太
Switch with me, Kouta!
コラ　見るな！　ストップ！　やめろ
Hey! Stop looking!
Stop!
Stop it now!
特に水野…
≪（親猫）おお　この宿におったんか
Especially at Mizuno!
You're staying here?
お前ら…
You guys!
おおきに　お昼はありがとう
Thanks for lunch.
おおきに　お礼のプチ情報
Thanks. I'll give you a tip.
そっちのすき間の方が
よう見えるで　女湯
The hole over there has a better view of the women's side.
〈いかん　俺
悪魔のささやきにのるな俺〉
N-No! Don't give in to the devil's temptations!
〈あの清く優しく汚れなき水野に〉
Peeping on the pure and noble Mizuno is a sin I mustn't commit!
〈のぞきなどという
ハレンチな行為は…〉
しかし　ちょっとだけなら…
B-But... maybe just a bit...
てか　せっかくのお猫様の勧め
断っちゃ　また呪いが進むかも…
Besides, if I ignore the cats' advice, the curse might get worse.
I have no choice!
仕方あるまい！
あ　行った
He did it.
仕方ないんだ　断腸の思いだ
I have no choice.
This is really painful.
仕方ないんだーッ
Really! No choice!
K-K-Kousaka-kun!
こッ　高坂君
いや　これは　その…
決して　のぞいてたわけじゃない
W-Well, I wasn't trying to peep or anything!
混浴じゃない？　的な話を聞いてね
I heard this might be a mixed bath...
てめえ～ッ！→
You bastard!
いい度胸だーッ！
You've got some nerve!
（加奈子）…たく　高バカのヤロー
どこまでも調子こきやがって
That damn Koubaka!
He gets so carried away!
カナちゃ～ん　私　私…
Kana-chan!
I... I...
〈（加奈子）やれやれ　この様子じゃ
当分アイツとも進展なさそうだな〉
Sheesh, I guess nothing's happened between them yet.
明日は嵐山の方にでも行こうぜ
Let's take Koubaka to visit Arashiyama tomorrow.
高バカも誘って
えッ？
We'll make him buy us a lot to make up for today!
今日のわび入れに
たっぷりおごらせてやるさ
だね
Yeah.
でも　ちょっと　かわいそうかな
高坂君
But I feel bad for him too.
Don't!
痛ーい　やったな　それ！
That hurt!
Payback time!
There!
ハズレ！
Missed!
Let me in on it too!
やるなら私も
そうよ　寝られなくなっちゃったし
Yeah, now I can't sleep!
Why you!
（担任）高坂　反省してんのか　お前
Kousaka! Are you really sorry?
すいません
Yeah, sorry.
〈これもアレルゲンの呪いか〉
I-Is this part of the curse?
I hate this school trip!
嫌いだ　修学旅行なんて！
Oh, the sound of the bell from Gion-shoja!
（凪）あ　祇園精舎の鐘の声
あ　ポン！→
Ah, bom.
諸行無常の響きあり～
It's a reminder that all things must pass.
（爺）お上手です　お嬢様
Well read, Mistress.
わが美しきホームタウン　京都よ
My beautiful hometown, Kyoto!
帰ってきたぞ　不本意ながら！
I've come back against my will!
Haruhiko...
お前と相談して決めたかったよ
そうだんす
I wanted to talk about this beforehand.
Yeah?
I'm Eiko.
栄子どすえ～
ヒナ子どすえ～
I'm Hinako.
Welcome.
おいでやす～
≪（鈴）はあ～
いいなあ　お兄ちゃん
I'm envious of my brother.
Traditional cuisine at Gion,
祇園のおばんざい　四条のおだんご
錦市場のお茶漬け　あ～ん
dumplings at Shijo,
rice with green tea at Nishiki Ichiban...
Kyoto-style veggies at Ohara,
大原の京野菜　叡山の湯葉
tofu skin at Hiei-san,
and... and...
それに　それに…
（母）安心おし！→
Don't worry!
おみやげリストなら
ちゃんと渡しておいたわ
I made sure to give him a souvenir list.
I secretly saved up just for this day!
母さん　この日のために
ちゃーんと
ヘソクリためたんだから
ヘソクリを京みやげに？→
You spent your secret savings on souvenirs from Kyoto?!
You're awesome!
よッ　太っ腹！
（ニャムサス）にゃれにゃれ
Oh dear.
You're on your own today.
（先生）本日は
班ごとの自由行動となる
Meet back here at 5 PM.
集合時間は５時
遅れた場合は荷物を点検するぞ
If you're late, you'll have to help check the bags.
≪（生徒達）ええ～ッ
Kouta, let's get going.
晃太　早く行こうぜ
誰とメールしてんの？
Who are you texting?
うん？　ウチの彼女
My girlfriend.
He didn't even hesitate!
〈サラリと言うた！〉
〈素直にガッテム〉
Seriously, God damn it!
She sent me a tip.
で　ヤツからお前らに耳寄り情報だ
えッ？
「ネットで調べたところ
京都のオススメ　デートスポットは」
According to her net searches,
the benches along the Kamogawa River are the best dating site in Kyoto.
「鴨川沿いのベンチ
カップルだらけでムード満点よ」
The place is filled with couples, and the mood is awesome.
ムード…　満点？
The mood... is awesome...
《わあ～　キレイだね　夜景》
It's a beautiful view.
Yeah.
《いや　水野　君の方がキレイだよ》
No, Mizuno, you're more beautiful.
《えッ？　はう～　ムード満点！》
I love this mood!
I love you!
《やっぱ好きやねん！》
Hey, Junpei!
≪（加奈子）おい　潤平
今日　私らと回んねえ？
大勢の方が　ぜってー楽しいし
Do you wanna hang around with us?
More people means more fun.
Right, Kaede?
だろ？　楓
うッ　うん
Y-Yeah.
C-Could this be...
〈これは　もしや〉
We'd be happy to!
謹んで　お受けします
イエーイ！
よーし　昨日の礼
たっぷりさせてもらうぜ
Great!
We'll make you pay for what happened yesterday!
Nothing's better than dumplings!
（加奈子）何よりもダンゴだな
Sumiyoshi! How much do you plan to eat?!
テメエ　どんだけ食えば気が…
Huh? Don't talk back to me, you peeping Tom!
口ごたえできるのか？
この　のぞきボーイ
Look! Boats!
見て　舟だよ　舟
そうだね
Yeah.
〈いかん
このままでは　みやげ代が…〉
Crap! At this rate, the souvenir money will...
You're a useless son!
《バカ息子！》
Hey, isn't that the cursed guy we heard about?
あれ　噂の罰当たりじゃねえ？
マジ　マジ？
Really? Really?
The situation is getting worse!
さらにピーンチ！
Yeah!
うおっしゃーッ　腹もふくれたし
その辺　見て回っぞ
Now that I'm full, let's head out!
Come on!
ほら
待てってば　住吉
Wait, Sumiyoshi!
I'm not—
あ～　何だよ
行っちゃうの　つまんない
Huh?
Is he leaving?
That's no fun.
〈この勢い　悪くねえかも〉
Her forcefulness...
It's not so bad!
Let's go, Kousaka-kun.
行こう　高坂君
Mizuno!
水野　アハハハッ
俺らも～
Us too!
That's a great shot.
日光写真でござる
Really, this school trip is the best.
〈やっぱ修学旅行はサイコーだ〉
〈そういえば確かこの辺に
渡されたリストの店が…　と〉
By the way, I think there's a shop on my list around here.
Mommy!
うわ～ん
Where am I?
ここどこや？
迷子になってもうた
I'm lost!
N-No!
〈いかん　情にほだされては…〉
Don't feel sorry for him!
（加奈子）何だこれ　ウケる
超いい～
What's this? It's cracking me up!
I love it!
Yeah?
そう？
おう潤平　これ買っ…
Hey Junpei, buy—
Sorry, I need to do something.
わりい　俺ちょっと　用事が…
Go on without me.
とにかく先に帰っててくれよ
じゃ…
Bye.
おい　潤平
高坂君
Hey, Junpei...
Kousaka-kun...
チェッ　何だよ　アイツ
What's the matter with him?!
あ～あ　心配だな～
潤平君　方向オンチだしな～
Hm, I'm worried.
He has no sense of direction.
Yeah, this is bad.
確かに困ったな～　メシまでに
帰らねえと連帯責任だしな～
We'll all be held responsible if we don't return by dinner.
Ugh...
おおきに　すんまへんなあ
Thanks!
Sorry for the trouble.
で？　何か思い出せねえの？
So, can't you remember anything?
Like your owner's name, or a landmark?
飼い主の名前とか家の目印とか
…って　あれ？
うわ～　かわいい！
It's so cute!
≪（加奈子）チビ猫だ　チビ猫
It's a little kitten!
高坂君　ゴメン
気になったからついてきちゃった
Sorry, Kousaka-kun.
We got worried and followed you.
用事って何だよ？　しゃーねえから
ついてきてやったんだぜ
Wh-What do you have to do?
I guess we can help.
おッ　お前ら…
Y-You guys!
≪（マサ）ニャ～ン
どこやーッ？　小政ーッ！
Where are you, Komasa!
アイツは…
That's...
Komas—
小政…　小政！　無事やったんか
Komasa! You're safe!
Koma... sa?
コマサ？
Dad!
（小政）おとーん！
Komasa!
小政ーッ！
イエス！
Yes!
フォーリンラヴ！
Hole in one!
あの子のパパかな？
Is that the kitten's daddy?
潤平ひょっとして
迷子の面倒見てたとか？
Junpei, were you taking care of a lost kitten?
まあな
よかったね
Y-Yeah.
I'm so glad!
あんたはんは…　えろうすんまへん
息子までお世話に
Hey, it's you!
Thanks a lot.
You even helped my son.
おッ　おう…
I want to return the favor.
ご恩返しや　ついてきとくれやす
Come with us.
きとくれやーす
Come!
なんか
ついてこいって感じじゃねえ？
Doesn't it look like they want us to follow them?
偶然　当たってんだよね
By coincidence, you're right.
Let's go!
行ってみよう
おう
Yeah!
Hey!
さあさあ　ここですわ
ですわ～
Come this way.
This way.
こッ　ここは…
I-Is this...
一ノ瀬組って…
Ichinose Clan
Isn't this the Ichinose Group...
≪（加奈子）本家～ッ！？
It's the clan leader's house!
急げ！　念のため身代金の手配を
Hurry!
Prepare ransom money just in case!
If anything has happened to Komasa...
小政の身に何かあったら…
Senpai!
≪（楓・加奈子）せんぱーい！
おお　奇遇だな　君達
What a coincidence.
小政！
それに行方不明だったマサ！
Komasa!
And the long-lost Masa!
ニャ～ン
じゃ　こいつが身を寄せてたっつー
常磐町の知り合いは…
Then, the friend he was staying with in Tokiwa was...
（ジョセフィーヌ）あんさんら
何してんねん？　こないなとこで
What are you guys doing here?
So it was those guys.
やっぱり　この方でした
≪（加奈子）はあ～
ここがナギー先輩の京都の実家
This is your home in Kyoto?
（凪）うん　毎年　今時分は
一族の総会でな
Yeah.
We have a clan meeting every year around this time.
奇遇ですね
What an amazing coincidence.
乾杯！
Cheers!
Glad you're here.
よう来た　これが俺の恋女房
シンディや
This is my lovely wife, Cindy.
（シンディ）いらっしゃいませ
Welcome.
Please make yourself at home, Kousaka-sama.
どうぞお楽になってくださいまし
はあ
Yeah.
〈…って　奥さん　いたんかい〉
You had a wife?
（シンディ）このマサは
大変よき男なのですが→
Masa is a great cat, but he has one big fault.
１つだけ欠点が…
（お銀）浮気しよって
こん子がおなかん中におったんに
You playboy!
I was still carrying Komasa then!
S-Stop it, Okinu!
よせ　お銀　ガキの前で…
ウワキって何～？
Don't talk like that in front of the child!
What's a playboy?
何だかなあ
Man...
で　しばらく俺んとこで
預かっとったんよ
So I looked after him for a while.
けど　小政が無事生まれたと聞いて
いてもたってもいられず
But when I heard that Komasa had been born safe and sound, I really wanted to—
You'd better not have seen that bitch!
あの女とは会うてないやろうね？
Ugh!
ギクッ
なんやと？
Why are you reacting like that?!
I didn't! I swear!
会うてへん　ホンマや！
A domestic battle doesn't make a tasty meal, even for cats.
夫婦ゲンカは猫も食わへんな
あら　おなかが　おすき？
Oh, are you hungry?
キャットフードがないならお菓子でも
ちゃうて
If we're out of cat food, we can find some snacks.
That's not it.
ホンマかわええわ　お前
You're so cute!
You need to be careful as well.
あんさんも目移りはアカンで
二兎を追う者…　ちゃう
三兎を追う者　一兎も得ずや
If you go after two hares... or three hares, you won't catch any.
ああ？　何のことだ？
Huh?
What are you talking about?
やれやれ
相変わらずのニブチンやな
Oh dear.
You're as dense as ever.
じゃあ　ナギー先輩
また学校でな
Bye, Nagi-senpai.
Yeah, see you again at school.
ごちそうさまでした
Thank you for the snacks.
≪（爺）ブブーン！
≪（凪）ブブーン！
しかし
偶然とは恐ろしいものですな
Anyway, coincidence is very powerful.
まさか　この広い京都で…
まったくだ
In this big city of Kyoto...
Seriously.
かわいい後輩　楓達には悪いが
I'm sorry for my dear kouhai, Kaede,
私と高坂は
結ばれる運命なのかもしれん！
but Kousaka and I may be destined partners after all!
美しい　美しいぞ
マイ　レッド　ディスティニー　糸！
That's beautiful!
So beautiful!
My red thread of destiny!
〈高坂潤平　やはり油断ならぬ男〉
Kousaka Junpei...
We really must keep a close eye on him.
Man, I'm so full!
いや～　腹いっぱいだぜ
これじゃ旅館のメシ　入んねえな
I won't be able to eat dinner at the inn.
あッ　見て　夕日がキレイだよ　ほら
Oh, look!
The setting sun is so pretty! See!
わあ～
〈（潤平・加奈子）
カッ　カップルだらけ〉
S-So many couples...
This will be a great memory too.
や～　これもいい思い出だね
うんうん！
〈もし　水野と…〉
If Mizuno and...
〈潤平と…〉
If Junpei and...
〈（潤平・加奈子）
２人っきりで　ここに来てたら…〉
I were here alone...
大変！　もう集合時間だよ
先生に怒られちゃう
Oh no! We were supposed to be back at the inn by now!
We're in trouble!
だッ　だな！
急ごうぜ！
Y-Yeah!
Let's hurry!
みッ　水野
うん？
M-Mizuno!
U-Um...
あの…　これ
うん？
Here.
ほら　この間のお礼
In return for last time, you know.
映画村で買ったんだけどさ
気に入るかどうか　その…
I-I bought it at the Studio Park.
I don't know if you'll like it or not...
てつにいーッ！
Tetsu-nii!
ありがとう　これ探してたの
えッ？
Thank you!
I've been looking for this!
全種類ゲットだぜーッ
Now I have the whole set!
そうか　よかっ…
高バカ　私のは？
R-Really.
That's—
Koubaka, where's mine?
おめえには　さんざんおごったろ
I already bought you a ton of food.
Ｎ７００系パーンチ！
Model N700 Punch!
Note: The N700 is the newest model of Shinkansen (Japanese high-speed train).
何すんだよ！
What was that for?!
≪（晃太）さッ　帰るか
≪（晴彦）だね
Let's go home.
Yup!
natsu no kaze kirameku machi ni
In this town where the wind sparkles,
nigemizu oikakeru anata no sugata
I see you chasing a mirage.
shinkokyuu shite oikakeru kedo
You take a deep breath and keep chasing it.
chiisaku kieteyuku senaka ni sotto tsubuyaita
I whisper to your back as you get further away.
nemurenai yoru ni me wo tojite
When I close my eyes on sleepless nights,
omoiegaku mirai niwa
and imagine my future,
futari no egao sore igai ni mou mienai
I can only see the two of us smiling together.
konnani setsunai kimochi
This really sweet, painful thought...
kizuite kurenakutemo
Even if you never notice it,
kokoro ni sotto negau dake
I just wish for it in my mind.
ashita ni nareba kanau hazu!
I'm sure it'll come true tomorrow!
surechigatta shunkan ni
At the moment we passed by each other,
waraikakete kureta ne
you gave me a smile.
soredake de mune ga atsui
Just that makes my heart glow,
shiawase dakara
because I'm happy...
because I'm happy.
Strawberry Tears
Strawberry tears.
Today's Nyan Koma.
Today's Mew view
Ichinose Clan Meeting
Stand back!
Here comes the Don's family!
My daughter! Look at these men!
And choose your husband!
Sorry!
The clan meeting was held to find her a husband.
What's the matter with this family?
Shounenji in Nishijin is also known as the Cat Temple.
Mew view
It also features a great pine tree known as the Cat Pine.
Now, the next Nyan Koi...
I'm home.
おひけえなすって！
You were out late, dear.
組長ご一家の　おなりーッ！
Welcome...
home.
Wait, why are you at my place?!
（凪の父）
我が娘よ　この男どもの中から
What's with that attitude?
We're doing you a favor by bringing you a cat in need!
（凪の母）むこ殿を　さあさあ！
まっぴらごめん！
A cat in need?
〈一ノ瀬組の総会は　お嬢様に
むこを取らせるためのもの〉
Yes.
I want to be able to catch sparrows.
なんやの　この一家
Next Nyan Koi, 8th nyan-ko,
京都西陣の称念寺は
猫寺として有名
"Chariots of the Burning Private Tutor."
境内には猫松と呼ばれる
立派な松の木もあるよ
Are all boys interested in girls' underwear?
The Burning Private
Instruction Runner